<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
      <title>Recent Content on Global Constant </title>
      <generator uri="https://hugo.spf13.com">Hugo</generator>
    <link>http://blog.scnay.com/index.xml/</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
    
    <updated>Sat, 22 Nov 2014 16:00:00 UTC</updated>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Eclectic Human</title>
      <link>http://blog.scnay.com/2014/11/22/eclectic-human</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2014 16:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.scnay.com/2014/11/22/eclectic-human</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last month I started writing a newsletter called &lt;a href=&#34;http://eclectichuman.scnay.com/&#34;&gt;An Eclectic
Human&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s a place to talk about community, philosophy, and being a better human. But
I&amp;rsquo;m not what makes it interesting. I share something each week that I&amp;rsquo;ve been
thinking about or trying in my life, and my lovely readers (including, perhaps,
you) write back and discuss the topic. Then the following week everyone gets to
read the thoughts of the other community members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So far, we&amp;rsquo;ve talked about
&lt;a href=&#34;http://eclectichuman.scnay.com/letters/2014/11/06/danny-and-reuven/&#34;&gt;books&lt;/a&gt; and
&lt;a href=&#34;http://eclectichuman.scnay.com/letters/2014/11/13/what-type-of-human-wed-like-to-be/&#34;&gt;music&lt;/a&gt;
we love, how to &lt;a href=&#34;http://eclectichuman.scnay.com/letters/2014/10/23/the-steel-man/&#34;&gt;communicate with compassion&lt;/a&gt;,
what it means to remember the past and why it&amp;rsquo;s sometimes
&lt;a href=&#34;http://eclectichuman.scnay.com/letters/2014/11/20/the-high-school-boy-who-bore-my-name/&#34;&gt;better to forget&lt;/a&gt;,
and much more. I&amp;rsquo;ve learned a lot so far, and I think you might enjoy it too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Would you like to join us on this journey? Just subscribe below.
Newsletters go out on Thursdays.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;form style=&#34;text-align: center; border: 1px solid #ccc; padding: 3px; margin: 3px 3%; background-color: #4882A3; color: #ccc&#34; action=&#34;https://tinyletter.com/snay2&#34; method=&#34;post&#34; target=&#34;popupwindow&#34; onsubmit=&#34;window.open(&#39;https://tinyletter.com/snay2&#39;, &#39;popupwindow&#39;, &#39;scrollbars=yes,width=800,height=600&#39;);return true&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://tinyletter.com/snay2&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; style=&#34;color: #fff; font-weight: bold;&#34;&gt;An Eclectic Human&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;label for=&#34;tlemail&#34;&gt;Enter your email address to subscribe to the newsletter:&lt;/label&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;input type=&#34;text&#34; name=&#34;email&#34; id=&#34;tlemail&#34; /&gt;
&lt;input type=&#34;hidden&#34; value=&#34;1&#34; name=&#34;embed&#34;/&gt;
&lt;button type=&#34;submit&#34; value=&#34;Subscribe&#34;&gt;Subscribe&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: smaller;&#34;&gt;powered by &lt;a href=&#34;https://tinyletter.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;TinyLetter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/form&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>17:05</title>
      <link>http://blog.scnay.com/2013/08/16/1705</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2013 09:24:04 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.scnay.com/2013/08/16/1705</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;He sits nestled between the window and two harried businessmen,&lt;br /&gt;
Sunk into an uncomfortable beige chair&lt;br /&gt;
One foot planted atop the heating vent on the wall&lt;br /&gt;
A half-read book open in his lap,&lt;br /&gt;
Perused only by shut eyelids.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The salesman across the aisle is closing the day&amp;rsquo;s last deal&lt;br /&gt;
Which transpires here because&lt;br /&gt;
The children expect him at 6.&lt;br /&gt;
The woman behind him animatedly explicates impending adventures&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;to her seat-mate.&lt;br /&gt;
And a man with serene but exhausted comportment&lt;br /&gt;
Gazes fondly, silently&lt;br /&gt;
At no one in particular.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But our friend, couched in the warm sunlight of his wall of glass&lt;br /&gt;
Is napping insistently,&lt;br /&gt;
Head bobbing up and down, up&lt;br /&gt;
And down,&lt;br /&gt;
Tuning his ears only to the ceiling&amp;rsquo;s bold double tone&lt;br /&gt;
And the conductor&amp;rsquo;s scratchy call,&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;ldquo;Now arriving.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eventually the voice in the roof will name this man&amp;rsquo;s little town,&lt;br /&gt;
The intermittent nonsense of his dreams will cease,&lt;br /&gt;
The blindly-read book will close,&lt;br /&gt;
And the uncomfortable sunlit perch will discharge its occupant,&lt;br /&gt;
Who will descend groggily to the platform and watch&lt;br /&gt;
As the train roars away.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Defense of Marriage: The Supreme Court&#39;s Rulings and Their Implications</title>
      <link>http://blog.scnay.com/2013/06/26/in-defense-of-marriage</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2013 15:53:07 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.scnay.com/2013/06/26/in-defense-of-marriage</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;The Supreme Court &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.npr.org/blogs/thetwo-way/2013/06/26/195857796/supreme-court-strikes-down-defense-of-marriage-act&#34;&gt;ruled today&lt;/a&gt; that the Defense of Marriage Act, which denies some federal benefits to citizens in legal, state-recognized homosexual marriages, is unconstitutional. It also ordered the Ninth Circuit Court of Appeals to dismiss the Proposition 8 case it previously ruled on, effectively overturning the ballot initiative and making same-sex marriage legal again in California.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The DOMA decision is perhaps the most important victory so far for proponents of gay marriage, as it removes from the federal government the ability to define marriage and returns that power to the states.&lt;span style=&#34;vertical-align: super; font-size: 80%;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#f1&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Its immediate implications will only affect same-sex couples living in (or married by) states that recognize such unions, but it won&amp;rsquo;t be long before other states follow the &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Same-sex_marriage_law_in_the_United_States_by_state&#34;&gt;precedent&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Belief&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a Mormon, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.lds.org/topics/same-gender-attraction?lang=eng&#34;&gt;I believe&lt;/a&gt; homosexual activity to be morally wrong in the same way as adultery and fornication. But sexual orientation is not a choice, and I have no qualms with anyone being gay or lesbian. Only by acting on these feelings do they move into the realm of moral decision-making. Despite my personal principles, however, I can still support the Supreme Court of the United States or a state government that chooses to recognize same-sex marriages. Here&amp;rsquo;s why.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I happen to believe that drinking alcohol and smoking are wrong. I don&amp;rsquo;t do either one. But the government can make those things legal without affecting my beliefs. Society can make them acceptable or even normal without influencing my behavior. Religious people, including Mormons, fought to keep Prohibition early last century. They failed, but that hasn&amp;rsquo;t impeded their abstinence in the time since. Nothing in their lives changed with the policy, and it&amp;rsquo;s difficult to prove whether American society is any better or worse as a result.&lt;span style=&#34;vertical-align: super; font-size: 80%;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#f2&#34;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;Precedent&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The civil rights movement occurred in the United States over 50 years ago, and remnants of discrimination still exist in our culture today. Reason eventually triumphed over the bigots who fought equality under the law for all races. The gay marriage movement has many parallels to that dark period of discrimination, and it will hold similar status in history when it succeeds. It&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.deseretnews.com/article/865573814/Huntsman-backs-gay-marriage-calls-for-conservatives-to-push-issue.html?pg=all&#34;&gt;politically inexpedient&lt;/a&gt; to fight it anymore. Even the LDS Church, once a formidable advocate of California&amp;rsquo;s Proposition 8, has &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.motherjones.com/politics/2013/04/prop-8-mormons-gay-marriage-shift&#34;&gt;softened its stance&lt;/a&gt; in recent years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the late 1800s, Mormons were on the other side of a &lt;a href=&#34;http://faithful.staynalive.com/2013/02/the-marriage-debate-mormons-have-been.html&#34;&gt;marriage definition battle&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span style=&#34;vertical-align: super; font-size: 80%;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#f3&#34;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; We wanted the right to practice polygamy but the United States denied it. In 1890, the leaders of the Church &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/1890_Manifesto&#34;&gt;issued a manifesto&lt;/a&gt; that discontinued polygamy as a matter of Church policy. Only then was Utah allowed to become a state. Having seen both sides of marital discrimination in the government, I would expect more sympathy from my LDS compatriots to this modern-day civil rights debate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_2&#34;&gt;A Social Experiment&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have no problem with any federal or state government recognizing or allowing same-sex marriage. I&amp;rsquo;m happy for those who will exercise this new right and build loving relationships. I may not agree with the morality of their decision, but I understand it, and their choices will not prevent me from living life the way I think is right. I can share my moral views and encourage others to follow them, but I cannot force them on anyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We don&amp;rsquo;t yet know what effect gay marriage will have on the fabric of society, just as with many similar questions in the past. As Ray Douthat &lt;a href=&#34;http://douthat.blogs.nytimes.com/2012/06/11/gay-parents-and-the-marriage-debate/&#34;&gt;famously wrote&lt;/a&gt; in 2012,&lt;span style=&#34;vertical-align: super; font-size: 80%;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#f4&#34;&gt;4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;ldquo;Same-sex marriage is a social experiment, and like most experiments it will take time to understand its consequences.&amp;rdquo;&lt;span style=&#34;vertical-align: super; font-size: 80%;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#f5&#34;&gt;5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; If society wants to try this experiment, I say good luck.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: 85%;&#34;&gt;&lt;a name=&#34;f1&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; A decision that ought to be celebrated by proponents of limited government, including Republicans who ultimately oppose gay marriage.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: 85%;&#34;&gt;&lt;a name=&#34;f2&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; A similar course of events may play out with some facets of the current &amp;ldquo;war on drugs&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: 85%;&#34;&gt;&lt;a name=&#34;f3&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Jesse Stay does a good job explaining the history and current thinking in the Church about marriage equality, but I don&amp;rsquo;t share his conclusion.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: 85%;&#34;&gt;&lt;a name=&#34;f4&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Dallin H. Oaks, a member of the Quorum of the Twelve Apostles in the LDS Church, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.lds.org/general-conference/2012/10/protect-the-children.p32-33&#34;&gt;quoted this essay&lt;/a&gt; in the Church&amp;rsquo;s October 2012 general conference, but he argued a point opposite Douthat, who writes, &amp;ldquo;a number of studies have suggested that gay parenting may be an exception to this rule [that being raised by a married biological mother and father produces the best developmental outcome], and that the outcomes of children raised by homosexual couples may be identical to children raised by married biological parents.&amp;rdquo; There simply isn&amp;rsquo;t enough evidence yet to conclude empirically whether gay marriage is a poor or suitable alternative to traditional marriage. For those who believe the Apostle&amp;rsquo;s claim to divine revelation (as I do), this question is easier to resolve.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: 85%;&#34;&gt;&lt;a name=&#34;f5&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; While I believe the best outcome for the world at large would be for everyone to adhere to the principles taught by Jesus Christ, that will obviously not happen anytime soon. For now, I think it better for us to respect each other&amp;rsquo;s beliefs and decisions while seeking the best compromises to let us live in harmony.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Definition of a Friend</title>
      <link>http://blog.scnay.com/2013/02/21/definition-of-a-friend</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2013 10:43:18 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.scnay.com/2013/02/21/definition-of-a-friend</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When I was in junior high, an admired teacher gave me a beautiful book of friendship quotes. One that particularly struck me began, &amp;ldquo;What is a friend? I will tell you&amp;hellip;.Your soul can be naked with him.&amp;rdquo; The entire poem is insightful, but that sentence was especially compelling. A friend requires no pretenses, expects nothing more than what you are. He understands the flaws and contradictions in your character and accepts you notwithstanding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have since searched extensively for the source of the poem, which seems to be shrouded in mystery. Many have claimed authorship&lt;span style=&#34;vertical-align: super; font-size: 80%;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#f1&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; over the years, but the &lt;a href=&#34;http://books.google.com/books?id=FnstAQAAMAAJ&amp;pg=RA3-PA26#v=onepage&amp;q&amp;f=false&#34;&gt;earliest source&lt;/a&gt; I can find cites Dr. Frank Crane in the 1910s. Here is the transcription from that publication:&lt;span style=&#34;vertical-align: super; font-size: 80%;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#f2&#34;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DEFINITION OF A FRIEND&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
By Dr. Frank Crane&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is a friend?&lt;br /&gt;
I will tell you.&lt;br /&gt;
It is a person with whom you dare to be yourself.&lt;br /&gt;
Your soul can go naked with him.&lt;br /&gt;
He seems to ask of you to put on nothing, only to be what you are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He does not want you to be better or worse.&lt;br /&gt;
When you are with him you feel as a prisoner feels who has been declared innocent.&lt;br /&gt;
You do not have to be on your guard.&lt;br /&gt;
You can say what you think, express what you feel.&lt;br /&gt;
He is shocked at nothing, offended at nothing, so long as it is genuinely you.&lt;br /&gt;
He understands those contradictions in your nature that lead others to misjudge you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With him you breathe freely.&lt;br /&gt;
You can take off your coat and loosen your collar.&lt;br /&gt;
You can avow your little vanities and envies and hates and vicious sparks, your meanness and absurdities, and in opening them up to him they are lost, dissolved in the white ocean of his loyalty.&lt;br /&gt;
He understands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You do not have to be careful.&lt;br /&gt;
You can abuse him, neglect him, berate him.&lt;br /&gt;
Best of all, you can keep still with him.&lt;br /&gt;
It makes no matter.&lt;br /&gt;
He likes you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He is like fire, that purifies all you do.&lt;br /&gt;
He is like water, that cleanses all you say.&lt;br /&gt;
He is like wine, that warms you to the bone.&lt;br /&gt;
He understands, he understands, he understands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can weep with him, laugh with him, sin with him, pray with him.&lt;br /&gt;
Through and underneath it all he sees, knows and loves&amp;mdash;you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A friend, I repeat, is one with whom you dare to be yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: 85%;&#34;&gt;&lt;a name=&#34;f1&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Some who have claimed authorship include &lt;a href=&#34;http://rachellimalopes.wordpress.com/2009/06/05/what-is-a-friend-c-raymond-beran/&#34;&gt;Kristina Bruce&lt;/a&gt; in the 70s and &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.sermons.org/illustrations/f/friendship.htm&#34;&gt;C. Raymond Beran&lt;/a&gt; in the 90s. Their claims are tenuous. Frank Crane seems to be most often cited as the original author, and the Shoe Workers&amp;rsquo; Journal from 1916 (linked in the text) is the earliest source I can find with either the poem or the Crane byline.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: 85%;&#34;&gt;&lt;a name=&#34;f2&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; I corrected two typographical errors and added line breaks to increase readability.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using a git post-receive hook for easy production deploys</title>
      <link>http://blog.scnay.com/2013/02/20/using-a-git-post-receive-hook-for-easy-production-deploys</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2013 09:48:55 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.scnay.com/2013/02/20/using-a-git-post-receive-hook-for-easy-production-deploys</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have a git repository on my dev machine, which I use for developing and testing code locally. When I&amp;rsquo;m ready to deploy to production, I simply push that git repo to the server and use a post-receive hook there to move the code into the proper places. Here&amp;rsquo;s what my setup looks like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My &lt;code&gt;~/.ssh/config&lt;/code&gt; has a Host entry called &lt;code&gt;prod&lt;/code&gt; for the production server that specifies where it lives and how to authenticate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In &lt;code&gt;.git/config&lt;/code&gt;, I have a remote section for the production server:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;[remote &amp;quot;prod&amp;quot;]
    url = ssh://prod:~/web.git
    fetch = +refs/heads/*:refs/remotes/origin/*
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;web.git&lt;/code&gt; on the server is set up as a bare repository. In the &lt;code&gt;hooks&lt;/code&gt; folder, I have a &lt;code&gt;post-receive&lt;/code&gt; file like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;#!/bin/sh
# Check out the source tree without .git
GIT_WORK_TREE=/home/ubuntu/stage/web git checkout -f

# Turn off debug mode, if enabled
sed -i -e &amp;quot;/^DEBUG = True$/s/True/False/&amp;quot; /home/ubuntu/stage/web/settings.py

# You can do any other configuration here to transform the code
#  from development to production.

# Restart Apache
sudo apache2ctl restart
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Permissions are set on the &lt;code&gt;/home/ubuntu/stage/web&lt;/code&gt; folder and the &lt;code&gt;/etc/apache2/sites-enabled/&lt;/code&gt; file points to that folder as the DocumentRoot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s all it takes. Now every time I do a &lt;code&gt;git push prod master&lt;/code&gt; on my dev machine, the code is uploaded to the server, properly configured for a production environment, and fed to Apache.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ColdFusion 9 and IIS 7</title>
      <link>http://blog.scnay.com/2013/02/08/coldfusion-9-and-iis-7</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 11:34:34 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.scnay.com/2013/02/08/coldfusion-9-and-iis-7</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m installing a ColdFusion application and ran into a few issues. Here, mostly for my future reference, is the process of solving those problems.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ColdFusion was installed before IIS 7. As such, IIS didn&amp;rsquo;t have the correct handlers for ColdFusion files. Follow the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.codecurry.com/2009/09/installing-coldfusion-on-iis-7.html&#34;&gt;instructions on Codecurry&lt;/a&gt; to get that resolved. The post is dated (the screenshots are on Vista), but the general process is still correct. Make sure these IIS features get installed: ASP.NET, .NET Extensibility, CGI, ISAPI Filters, and ISAPI Extensions. Then run the ColdFusion Web Server Configuration Tool to perform the necessary IIS configuration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once that was working, I started getting HTTP 500 errors. In my case, ColdFusion was only set up to run in 32-bit mode, even though IIS and Windows Server 2008 R2 is 64-bit. To fix this, go into IIS Manager and select the Application Pool your website is using. Choose Advanced Settings and change Enable 32-Bit Applications to True. (If you prefer the command line, see &lt;a href=&#34;http://forums.iis.net/post/1912776.aspx&#34;&gt;these instructions&lt;/a&gt; for this change.)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Influential writing</title>
      <link>http://blog.scnay.com/2012/11/02/influential-writing</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2012 13:25:15 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.scnay.com/2012/11/02/influential-writing</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Scott Cowley on Twitter &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/scottcowley/status/264433138300760064&#34;&gt;posits&lt;/a&gt; that &amp;ldquo;You don&amp;rsquo;t earn the title of &amp;lsquo;well-read&amp;rsquo; by reading blog posts and news articles.&amp;rdquo; I mostly agree with his premise. Long-form printed literature is still instrumental in shaping the way we think and act as individuals and as a society. But modern evolutions of writing&amp;mdash;blog posts, essays, ebooks&amp;mdash;also have intellectually shaping capabilities. They both have place in the library of an educated, well-read citizen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some of the books that have profoundly influenced my thinking:
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Chosen&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;(Chaim Potok)&lt;/em&gt; for its exposition of true friendship and loyalty.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1984&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;(George Orwell)&lt;/em&gt;, ever more relevant an investigation of technology and government and the disaster they can create if left unchecked.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hamlet&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;(William Shakespeare)&lt;/em&gt;, if not merely for its quotability (&amp;ldquo;Alas, poor Yorick!&amp;rdquo;), serves as a tragic warning against greed and revenge.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Christmas Carol&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;(Charles Dickens)&lt;/em&gt;, a well-known classic with a prominent place on my annual reading list, extols the virtues of empathy and charity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Walden&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;(Henry David Thoreau)&lt;/em&gt;, which emphasizes the importance of self-reliance, contemplation, and introspection.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the short-form category, these pieces have had a similarly powerful effect on my life:
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.classicreader.com/book/769/1/&#34;&gt;The Mansion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;(Henry van Dyke)&lt;/em&gt;, a Christian short story about the proper use of wealth.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.codinghorror.com/blog/2012/05/buying-happiness.html&#34;&gt;Buying Happiness&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;(Jeff Atwood)&lt;/em&gt;, which explains how to make you and others happier through wise choices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://taylormali.com/poems-online/totally-like-whatever-you-know/&#34;&gt;Totally like whatever, you know?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;(Taylor Mali)&lt;/em&gt;, which powerfully discusses the need for clear thinking, speaking, and writing. &lt;a href=&#34;http://vimeo.com/3829682&#34;&gt;This video&lt;/a&gt; is the best way to experience the poem.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://danshipper.com/the-regret-fallacy&#34;&gt;The Regret Fallacy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;(Dan Shipper)&lt;/em&gt; &amp;ndash; make the best decisions you can and then be happy with them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2003/03/caring-for-your-introvert/302696/&#34;&gt;Caring for Your Introvert&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;(Jonathan Rauch)&lt;/em&gt;, a guide for introverts (like me) and their loved ones to understand how they think.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A book, a play, a poem, a short story, an article, two blog posts, and three novels. Plenty of variety.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIY standing desk</title>
      <link>http://blog.scnay.com/2012/10/15/diy-standing-desk</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2012 19:53:04 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.scnay.com/2012/10/15/diy-standing-desk</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A month ago I decided to build a standing desk for my computer at home. By the time I finish my day job, I&amp;rsquo;m tired of sitting. Here&amp;rsquo;s what I did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;http://iamnotaprogrammer.com/Ikea-Standing-desk-for-22-dollars.html&#34;&gt;Standesk 2200&lt;/a&gt; caught my attention because it&amp;rsquo;s made from Ikea parts totaling $30: two &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ikea.com/us/en/catalog/products/20011413/#/20011408&#34;&gt;side tables&lt;/a&gt; ($7.99 each), a &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ikea.com/us/en/catalog/products/20167961/#/90167477&#34;&gt;shelf&lt;/a&gt; ($5.99), and two &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ikea.com/us/en/catalog/products/56696109/#/80167473&#34;&gt;brackets&lt;/a&gt; ($4.00 each). Get a screwdriver, drill, level, and some wood screws (presumably already around the house) and put it together. Here&amp;rsquo;s what mine looks like:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://s3.amazonaws.com/scnay-images/globalconstant/standing-desk.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://s3.amazonaws.com/scnay-images/globalconstant/standing-desk.jpg&#34; title=&#34;My standing desk&#34; class=&#34;aligncenter&#34; width=&#34;500&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also put a small lamp behind the monitor for some &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.codinghorror.com/blog/2011/11/bias-lighting.html&#34;&gt;bias lighting&lt;/a&gt; and bought a $20 anti-fatigue mat to keep my feet happy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The built-in desk atop which this contraption sits is already weirdly high (34&amp;rdquo;), putting the top of the side tables at 52&amp;rdquo;. Even with that, I still needed to put a few books under the monitor to raise it to eye level on my six-foot-something self. The keyboard/mouse tray is mounted 11&amp;rdquo; up on the table legs. The shelf and books can easily be suited to your height.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So far the standing desk has been a good investment. My lower back bothers me infrequently now (aided by my customary lunchtime walks along the river near my office). It forces me to take breaks more often than I otherwise might, and sitting becomes a welcome relief. I move around more while typing, and of course I can easily, if discreetly, dance to my music.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can build this setup in its simplest form for $22 and the price of gas for an Ikea trip. If you can spare that (or even the exorbitant $50 I spent), it&amp;rsquo;s worth trying out to see if your posture and comfort improve. And it won&amp;rsquo;t require parting with a small fortune for a &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.geekdesk.com/&#34;&gt;GeekDesk&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.codinghorror.com/blog/2008/07/investing-in-a-quality-programming-chair.html&#34;&gt;Aeron chair&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Boone Gorges has two &lt;a href=&#34;http://teleogistic.net/2011/06/stand-for-something/&#34;&gt;good&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;http://teleogistic.net/2012/01/ikea-standing-desk/&#34;&gt;posts&lt;/a&gt; on why he built a standing desk (which also hails from Ikea). Read those for his take on its benefits and disadvantages.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New vim tricks</title>
      <link>http://blog.scnay.com/2012/09/27/new-vim-tricks</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 15:18:55 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.scnay.com/2012/09/27/new-vim-tricks</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been using Vim since 2006, and it&amp;rsquo;s still my favorite text editor. My current job requires me to live in Visual Studio, so I&amp;rsquo;m using &lt;a href=&#34;http://visualstudiogallery.msdn.microsoft.com/59ca71b3-a4a3-46ca-8fe1-0e90e3f79329&#34;&gt;VsVim&lt;/a&gt;, a mostly-compatible Vim mode layered on top of the Visual Studio editor. My &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/snay2/configs&#34;&gt;.vimrc file&lt;/a&gt;, plugins, and syntax files are on my GitHub account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since Vim is such an important part of my development toolset, I&amp;rsquo;m always interested to learn new tricks and techniques to make it more efficient. A coworker gave a presentation on Vim today. It was intended as an introduction, but he managed to teach me quite a few useful new things in the process. Here are a few of them:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;e&lt;/code&gt; Move to the last letter of the current word (useful with &lt;code&gt;w&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;b&lt;/code&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;%&lt;/code&gt; Move to the parenthesis/curly brace/square bracket corresponding to the one under the cursor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;f&amp;lt;character&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; Find the next (or previous, with &lt;code&gt;F&lt;/code&gt;) occurrence of the given character on this line&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;:g!//d&lt;/code&gt; Remove all lines not matching a search previously done with / (not in VsVim)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;CTRL+R &#34;&lt;/code&gt; Paste the unnamed register while in insert mode&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;diw&lt;/code&gt; With the cursor in the middle of a word, delete the word&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;c$&lt;/code&gt; Delete to the end of the line (or any other motion) and switch to insert mode&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;:55&lt;/code&gt; Move to line 55, opening any code folds if necessary (easier and more robust than &lt;code&gt;55gg&lt;/code&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Move to the line at the top (&lt;code&gt;H&lt;/code&gt;), bottom (&lt;code&gt;L&lt;/code&gt;), or center of the screen (&lt;code&gt;M&lt;/code&gt;), respectively&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;zz&lt;/code&gt; Center the current line in the screen, or move it to the top (&lt;code&gt;zt&lt;/code&gt;) or bottom (&lt;code&gt;zb&lt;/code&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are a few favorites that I&amp;rsquo;ve learned over the past few months:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;*&lt;/code&gt; Find the next occurrence of the current word&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;gqq&lt;/code&gt; Wrap the current line (or &lt;code&gt;gq&lt;/code&gt; for a visual block) to 80 characters, modifying line breaks if necessary. Useful for plain text documents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;=&lt;/code&gt; Normalize the code indentation for the selected block&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cost of ownCloud on S3 vs. Dropbox</title>
      <link>http://blog.scnay.com/2012/09/11/cost-of-owncloud-vs-dropbox</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 11:04:42 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.scnay.com/2012/09/11/cost-of-owncloud-vs-dropbox</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;UPDATE SEPTEMBER 2014: I receive a lot of requests to update this with current numbers. Especially after Dropbox&amp;rsquo;s change in late 2014 to 1 TB of storage, this would be a useful comparison to run again. Hopefully I&amp;rsquo;ll get around to it soon.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Part of my quest to &lt;a href=&#34;/2012/08/31/owning-my-data/&#34;&gt;own my data&lt;/a&gt; involves looking at alternatives to Dropbox. This sentence from their &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.dropbox.com/terms&#34;&gt;terms of service&lt;/a&gt; is disconcerting:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;We reserve the right to suspend or end the Services at any time, with or without cause, and with or without notice.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amazon Web Services is &lt;a href=&#34;http://aws.amazon.com/agreement/&#34;&gt;more explicit&lt;/a&gt; in the reasons and timeline for termination. Either party may terminate the agreement with 30 days notice, or Amazon may terminate it immediately &lt;em&gt;with notice&lt;/em&gt;, but only for specific reasons (mostly legal, regulatory, or contractual reasons). That is a much more transparent and comforting policy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://owncloud.org/&#34;&gt;ownCloud&lt;/a&gt; looks like a good alternative to run your own Dropbox-like system, complete with desktop syncing and a mobile app. You need a web server and enough storage, either that server itself or something like Amazon S3. I decided to investigate the financial feasibility of running ownCloud and ditching Dropbox.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For comparison, let&amp;rsquo;s consider the smallest Dropbox paid account (100 GB) and the equivalent amount of storage on Amazon S3.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dropbox&lt;/strong&gt;
Simple. 100 GB is &lt;strong&gt;$99.00&lt;/strong&gt;/year. No bandwidth costs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;S3&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;&lt;td&gt;Item&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Amount&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Price/GB&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Total&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Storage&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;100 GB&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;$0.125&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;$12.50&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Bandwidth in&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;50 GB&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;$0.00&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;$0.00&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Bandwidth out&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;50 GB&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;$0.120*&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;$5.88&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td colspan=&#34;3&#34;&gt;Total per month&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;$18.38&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td colspan=&#34;3&#34;&gt;Total per year&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$220.56&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
*The first GB of bandwidth out is free.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In short, with full utilization and ignoring the cost of running the server for the ownCloud software, S3 is 223% more expensive ($121.56 extra per year).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s look at a scenario with a more moderate usage of 25 GB (closer to what I&amp;rsquo;m using now). With Dropbox you&amp;rsquo;ll still pay the same price, but S3 will only charge for what you use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;&lt;td&gt;Item&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Amount&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Price/GB&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Total&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Storage&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;25 GB&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;$0.125&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;$3.13&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Bandwidth in&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;12 GB&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;$0.00&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;$0.00&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Bandwidth out&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;13 GB&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;$0.120*&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;$1.56&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td colspan=&#34;3&#34;&gt;Total per month&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;$4.69&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td colspan=&#34;3&#34;&gt;Total per year&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$56.28&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Using only a quarter of the 100 GB, we come in about $40 cheaper on S3 (still ignoring server costs).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you use about 40 GB, you come in close to the same price on S3 as on Dropbox.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;
In short, if you&amp;rsquo;re going to use the full 100 GB, it will save you tons of money to stay with Dropbox rather than run ownCloud and put the files on S3. You&amp;rsquo;ll have to weigh whether the higher price is worth the data ownership.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Veriphonification</title>
      <link>http://blog.scnay.com/2012/09/10/veriphonification</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 08:14:04 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.scnay.com/2012/09/10/veriphonification</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Perhaps I shouldn&amp;rsquo;t admit this publicly, but I like One Direction&amp;rsquo;s hit, &amp;ldquo;What Makes You Beautiful&amp;rdquo;. It&amp;rsquo;s catchy and has a positive lay. It also has a niggling logical fallacy:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;So c-come on,
You got it wrong.
&lt;strong&gt;To prove I&#39;m right,
I put it in a song.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s how this argument plays out:
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am a famous singer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Famous singers sing truth &lt;span style=&#34;font-size:smaller&#34;&gt;(the arguments necessary to deduce #2 from #1 are left as an exercise for the reader.)&lt;/smaller&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am singing about your beauty&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Therefore, you are beautiful. Q.E.D.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Appeal_to_authority&#34;&gt;Appeal to authority&lt;/a&gt;? Check. &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Argumentum_ad_populum&#34;&gt;Argumentum ad populum&lt;/a&gt;? Check (&amp;ldquo;everyone else in the room can see it&amp;rdquo;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also like Dr. K&amp;rsquo;s neologism, &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/cdknutson/status/245171349495107584&#34;&gt;veriphonification&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Owning my data</title>
      <link>http://blog.scnay.com/2012/08/31/owning-my-data</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2012 13:49:32 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.scnay.com/2012/08/31/owning-my-data</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Two months ago I decided to switch to Octopress. The idea of writing posts in Markdown and compiling them into a static site was appealing. The problem was that I had to be on my laptop at home to write a post, and I hadn&amp;rsquo;t quite mastered the quirks of the system. As a result, I haven&amp;rsquo;t written a blog post in two months, so I decided to switch back to WordPress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the main arguments in favor of a system like Octopress is &amp;ldquo;owning your data&amp;rdquo;. Rather than use a &amp;ldquo;free&amp;rdquo; hosted service that mines your writing to produce useful data for advertisers, it&amp;rsquo;s better to pay a little more (in time or money) and host your writing yourself. I moved this blog to my own server a few years ago, and it has been worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project Reclaim&lt;/strong&gt;
I read about Boone Gorges &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;http://projectreclaim.net/&#34;&gt;Project Reclaim&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rdquo; today and found it intriguing. He&amp;rsquo;s on a quest to get rid of as much proprietary software and systems as he can and regain control of his data. Seems like a worthwhile endeavor that I want to pursue as well. At the moment, the following services are my biggest hangups:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gmail,&lt;/strong&gt; not just for the email itself, but for Google Docs, OAuth-like logins, and Chrome Sync&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Twitter.&lt;/strong&gt; I am a heavy user of Twitter, but all the content I produce there disappears into Twitter&#39;s unsearchable archives after a matter of weeks. I need a more long-term solution in which I control my writing, but it needs to be just as easy to use (desktop, web, and mobile).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Instagram.&lt;/strong&gt; This is my platform of choice for photo sharing on Twitter and Facebook. I&#39;m currently porting everything to &lt;a href=&#34;http://snay2.openphoto.me/&#34;&gt;OpenPhoto&lt;/a&gt;, which lets you use your own S3 bucket to store the images. All the photos are stored in my own S3 account.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dropbox.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;http://owncloud.org/&#34;&gt;Owncloud&lt;/a&gt; looks like a great alternative, as they have desktop sync clients and possibly mobile clients in the works. As soon as version 5 comes out (which &lt;a href=&#34;http://blog.gapinthecloud.com/2012/06/10/configuring-external-storage-for-owncloud/&#34;&gt;supports using S3&lt;/a&gt; instead of the server&#39;s own disk space), I&#39;ll install it on this domain and give it a try.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are a few others, like Facebook (to which I rarely post anything) and Mint.com (no matter how trustworthy Intuit may be, I&amp;rsquo;d be better off using something like &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.youneedabudget.com/&#34;&gt;YNAB&lt;/a&gt; on my own machine and importing transactions manually). But I&amp;rsquo;m not as concerned about those at the moment. I first want to own all my important content production&amp;ndash;writing and photos&amp;ndash;and then I&amp;rsquo;ll work on the rest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Current objectives&lt;/strong&gt;
As I mentioned, I&amp;rsquo;m moving over to &lt;strong&gt;OpenPhoto&lt;/strong&gt;. A few days should tell me whether it&amp;rsquo;s good enough to replace Instagram.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m also going to create a new &lt;strong&gt;linkblog&lt;/strong&gt; on this domain. I had hoped to use Dave Winer&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;http://serversetup.reallysimple.org/&#34;&gt;Radio2&lt;/a&gt; software, since it stores its data on S3 and produces a &lt;a href=&#34;http://links.scripting.com/&#34;&gt;nice output&lt;/a&gt;. But it&amp;rsquo;s Windows- or Mac-only software, and I am only running Linux servers. I&amp;rsquo;m hoping I can find a good way to do that with WordPress. Once I do, I&amp;rsquo;ll start having those feed into Twitter and then use their native clients only for conversation and less-important writing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I may also decide to move away from &lt;strong&gt;Gmail&lt;/strong&gt;, choosing something like &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.rackspace.com/apps/email_hosting/rackspace_email/&#34;&gt;hosted email from Rackspace&lt;/a&gt;, about which I&amp;rsquo;ve heard good things. At $2/month, it&amp;rsquo;s an affordable alternative to Google&amp;rsquo;s data mining.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stories from the gay Mormon community</title>
      <link>http://blog.scnay.com/2012/06/18/stories-from-the-gay-mormon-community</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2012 12:15:18 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.scnay.com/2012/06/18/stories-from-the-gay-mormon-community</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve come across several stories from the historically reticent minority of homosexuals in the LDS community. Their writing deserves to be read; it has increased my compassion and respect for this misunderstood group.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the stories I&amp;rsquo;ve found most inspiring:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trevor Cook, who came out to his parents only after moving away to college. The post, written by his father: &lt;a href=&#34;http://mitchmayne.blogspot.com/2012/06/coming-out-as-lds-parent-of-gay-child.html&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;Coming Out as an LDS Parent of a Gay Child&amp;rdquo;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two gay men who each have a happy heterosexual marriage: Ty Mansfield (&lt;a href=&#34;http://ldsliving.com/story/68799-our-story-living-with-same-sex-attraction&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;Living with Same-sex Attraction: Our Story&amp;rdquo;&lt;/a&gt;) and Josh Weed (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.joshweed.com/2012/06/club-unicorn-in-which-i-come-out-of.html&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;Club Unicorn: In which I come out of the closet on our ten year anniversary&amp;rdquo;&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Brigham Young University group called Understanding Same Gender Attraction created a collection of insightful videos interviewing religious gay and lesbian students about their experiences coming to terms with their sexuality. This is the main video:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe class=&#34;youtube-player&#34; type=&#34;text/html&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; height=&#34;385&#34; src=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/embed/Ym0jXg-hKCI&#34; allowfullscreen frameborder=&#34;0&#34;&gt;
&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BYU hosted a panel discussion in April about homosexuality. Read the &lt;a href=&#34;http://universe.byu.edu/index.php/2012/04/05/department-of-sociology-hosted-gay-panel/&#34;&gt;Daily Universe article&lt;/a&gt; about it or &lt;a href=&#34;http://chriscarrollsmith.blogspot.com/2012/04/not-even-standing-room-at-byu-gay.html&#34;&gt;this blog post&lt;/a&gt;, which gives more detail about the participants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m pleased to see The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints updating its &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.mormonnewsroom.org/official-statement/same-gender-attraction&#34;&gt;stance on homosexuality&lt;/a&gt; to recognize accepted medical evidence that it is a biological trait, not a misguided choice.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Credit card numbers as channels</title>
      <link>http://blog.scnay.com/2012/05/23/credit-card-numbers-as-channels</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 20:51:27 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.scnay.com/2012/05/23/credit-card-numbers-as-channels</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Spotify and LinkedIn are hounding me to try their premium versions free for a month. I&amp;rsquo;d gladly oblige if I didn&amp;rsquo;t have to give them a credit card number. They&amp;rsquo;re secretly hoping I&amp;rsquo;ll forget to cancel my account before the month is up so they can charge me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want a way to give Spotify a unique financial &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.windley.com/archives/2012/02/event_channels.shtml&#34;&gt;channel&lt;/a&gt; that points back to a &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vendor_relationship_management&#34;&gt;VRM&lt;/a&gt; system operating on my behalf. In that system, I specify that the Spotify channel is good for 29 days; after that, it expires. Anytime before that, Spotify can negotiate a financial transaction through the channel, but once it has expired, the channel denies any transactions. I get to use Spotify Unlimited for a month and when they try to charge my credit card for the second month it fails. The trial ends and I&amp;rsquo;m satisfied.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The merchant doesn&amp;rsquo;t know whether a channel is valid until it attempts a transaction on that channel. LinkedIn and Spotify want a credit card number because they can trust its validity, so this may be an unsatisfactory solution for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The idea of channels still has a lot of merit from the consumer perspective, but it may need some nuance before it&amp;rsquo;s acceptable for merchants.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Magic Mouse on Windows 7 with Boot Camp</title>
      <link>http://blog.scnay.com/2012/05/01/using-magic-mouse-on-windows-7-with-boot-camp</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2012 10:27:39 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.scnay.com/2012/05/01/using-magic-mouse-on-windows-7-with-boot-camp</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m running Windows 7 on some Mac hardware with Boot Camp. The Magic Mouse didn&amp;rsquo;t work right out of the box, even though Windows seems to understand the Bluetooth device just fine. I used the following combination of processes to get the Magic Mouse to work:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First, install the mouse with the following steps: &lt;a href=&#34;https://discussions.apple.com/thread/2221427?threadID=2221427&amp;start=0&amp;tstart=0&#34;&gt;Magic Mouse Guide for Windows&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Second, get two-finger scrolling to work, with the updated Apple Bluetooth driver. I had a hard time finding this, but &lt;a href=&#34;http://forums.macrumors.com/showthread.php?t=911591&#34;&gt;here&#39;s a link that&#39;s still active&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Third, enable natural scrolling (because using Lion on a Mac for a year ruined me to normal old-school scrolling). I used an &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.howtogeek.com/57542/how-to-get-the-worst-os-x-lion-feature-in-windows-reverse-scrolling/&#34;&gt;AutoHotkey script&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s it. Took a lot more research than it should have. But hey, it works now.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>